<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Farady</title>
    <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Farady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:24:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.distribution-transformer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PAKISTAN PMI.SAHIWAL(Lahore)</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/pakistan-pmisahiwallahore/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/pakistan-pmisahiwallahore/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Oil Immersed Transformer(S11-25/10-0.4KV)</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/s11-25-10-0-4kv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:35:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/s11-25-10-0-4kv/</guid>
      <description>General oil immersed power transformer,based on know-how accumulated over decade years in oil immersed distribution transformer field, Farady’s oil-immersed transformers have been supplied to various industries including semiconductor, steel work, and petrochemical. Further, as an outstanding and comprehensive oil immersed distribution transformer solution provider, we respond to the oil immersed power transformer demanding requirements of our customers by developing and manufacturing both eco-friendly pole mounted distribution transformer and high-efficiency oil immersed power transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSG 10kV Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/csg-10kv-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/csg-10kv-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ECG 20MVA mobile AVR(Ghana)</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/ecg-20mva-mobile-avrghana/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/ecg-20mva-mobile-avrghana/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China National State Grid</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/china-national-state-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/china-national-state-grid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGCC Step Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgcc-step-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgcc-step-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SGCC 10kV Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgcc-10kv-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgcc-10kv-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Core Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/3d-core-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/3d-core-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General FARADY S11-M.RL, S13-M.RL series of three-dimensional triangular wound core transformer breaking the traditional planar structure, use symmetrical three-phase three-dimensional structure, the product is completely symmetrical three-phase core magnetic circuit reluctance greatly reduced, excitation current and significantly reduce the unload loss,which is a use of traditional materials,
but runs quieter, more compact energy-efficient transformers.
Its energy saving, environmental protection material on the outstanding performance of the province, and in full compliance with the energy policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Pole Mounted Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:22:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Farady power transformer Meets ANS/IEEE/CSA standard pole mounted transformer tank coating exceeds ANSI C57.12.31 single pole mounted transformer cover with a minimum dielectric strength of 8 kV pole mounted transformer tin-plated high-and low-voltage bushing terminals to accommodate aluminum or copper conductors single phase step down transformer with heavy-duty lifting lugs and hanger brackets per ANSI/CSA requirements
Farady power transformer single pole mounted transformer which is single phase pole mounted transformers（also call pole mounted transformer,single-phase transformer or single pole mounted transformer have been field proven to provide reliability quality single phase pole mounted transformer in various regions of the world, even in the harshest climates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amorphous Alloy Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:24:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General An amorphous metal transformer (AMT) is a type of energy efficient transformer found on electric grids. The magnetic core of this transformer is made with a ferromagnetic amorphous metal. The typical material (Metglas) is an alloy of iron with boron, silicon, and phosphorus in the form of thin (e.g. 25 µm) foils. These materials have high magnetic susceptibility, very low co ercivity and high electrical resistance. The high resistance and thin foils lead to low losses by eddy currents when subjected to alternating magnetic fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Oil Immersed Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:29:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General oil immersed power transformer,based on know-how accumulated over decade years in oil immersed distribution transformer field, Farady’s oil-immersed transformers have been supplied to various industries including semiconductor, steel work, and petrochemical. Further, as an outstanding and comprehensive oil immersed distribution transformer solution provider, we respond to the oil immersed power transformer demanding requirements of our customers by developing and manufacturing both eco-friendly pole mounted distribution transformer and high-efficiency oil immersed power transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SG&amp;DG Dry Type Transformers</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgdg-dry-type-transformers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:11:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/sgdg-dry-type-transformers/</guid>
      <description>General Dry type transformer is one of our mature products, which are manufactured in accordance with international and domestic market applications. DG and SG series single phase and three phase dry type transformer adopts high quality material and advancd technology, it has advantages of damp proof and convenient maintenance, it can be applied to such power transmission and distribution places like underground railway, high building, airport, station, wharf, enterprise, tunne, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dry Transformer Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/dry-type-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:14:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/dry-type-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General SC(B) series three phase resin-cast dry-type distribution transformer are in conformity with standard of IEC60076,with features of low loss, compact and light weight, low noise level,clamp-proof,anti-fouling,high mechanical strength, flame resisting, strong overload ability and low partial discharge quality,they are application to power transmission and distribution system,hotel,restaurant,commercial building,stadiums,chemical plants,stations,aiports,offshore drilling platforms,especially to heavy load centers and places with special fire protection requirements
Mainly Rating Types &amp;amp; Capacity
Three phase,
Two windings or three windings</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Pad Mounted Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-pad-mounted-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:20:19 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-pad-mounted-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General One of most important series of farady pad mount transformer is three phase pad mounted transformer, which have bigger capacity and wide application area.
Pad mount transformer are made in power ratings from around 75 to around 8000 kVA and often include built-in fuses and switches. Primary power cables may be connected with elbow connectors, which can be operated when energized using a hot stick and allows for flexibility in repair and maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>kiosk compact substation</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/kiosk-compact-substation/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:21:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/kiosk-compact-substation/</guid>
      <description>General YBW series prefabricated compact transformer is a kind of set of equipment which assembles the MV switch apparatus, prefabricated compact transformer, LV distribution equipment together according to fixed connection scheme. This series substation is suitable for neighborhood unit, hotel, large-scale work site and high building that the voltage is 11kV /15kV/17.5kV/34.5kV prefabricated compact transformer, the frequency is 50/60Hz and the prefabricated compact transformer capacity is under 2500kVA Standards: IEC60076,IEC1330, ANSI/IEEE C57.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Automatic Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:24:20 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-automatic-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Single phase Automatic voltage regulator regulate each phase sperately,automatic voltage regulator monitor and control MODBUS,DNP3 communicate protocol could connector step voltage regulator to smart grid,HT voltage regulator is best and ecomnoic solution for those long distance transmission and distribution line voltage drop problem.
Farady step voltage regulator are designed for reliable operation and ease of maintenance and are supplied with a full array of standard features for routine applications. HT voltage regulator optional accessories are available to ac-accommodate special application it is also suitable for the energy saving projects for railway and urban grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Step Voltage Regulator</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 11:24:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-step-voltage-regulator/</guid>
      <description>General Variation of voltage can have detrimental effects on Utilities and their customers. To prevent customer complaints, loss of revenue due to sub-normal voltage, and increased costs due to higher line losses, FARADY has designed the TVR Voltage Regulator with you, “The Utilities”, in mind. With over 10 years of experience, FARADY has designed the most reliable regulator ever assembled.
Ideally the distribution lines should to be able to keep the whole line of constant voltage, but in actual , the impedance of the distribution line will result in that the voltage of end and terminal is no the same .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
