<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oil immersed transformer on Farady</title>
    <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/category/oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oil immersed transformer on Farady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 14:17:53 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.distribution-transformer.com/category/oil-immersed-transformer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>3D Core Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/3d-core-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 15:43:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/3d-core-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General FARADY S11-M.RL, S13-M.RL series of three-dimensional triangular wound core transformer breaking the traditional planar structure, use symmetrical three-phase three-dimensional structure, the product is completely symmetrical three-phase core magnetic circuit reluctance greatly reduced, excitation current and significantly reduce the unload loss,which is a use of traditional materials,
but runs quieter, more compact energy-efficient transformers.
Its energy saving, environmental protection material on the outstanding performance of the province, and in full compliance with the energy policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single Phase Pole Mounted Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:22:40 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/single-phase-pole-mounted-transformer/</guid>
      <description>Farady power transformer Meets ANS/IEEE/CSA standard pole mounted transformer tank coating exceeds ANSI C57.12.31 single pole mounted transformer cover with a minimum dielectric strength of 8 kV pole mounted transformer tin-plated high-and low-voltage bushing terminals to accommodate aluminum or copper conductors single phase step down transformer with heavy-duty lifting lugs and hanger brackets per ANSI/CSA requirements
Farady power transformer single pole mounted transformer which is single phase pole mounted transformers（also call pole mounted transformer,single-phase transformer or single pole mounted transformer have been field proven to provide reliability quality single phase pole mounted transformer in various regions of the world, even in the harshest climates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amorphous Alloy Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:24:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/amorphous-alloy-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General An amorphous metal transformer (AMT) is a type of energy efficient transformer found on electric grids. The magnetic core of this transformer is made with a ferromagnetic amorphous metal. The typical material (Metglas) is an alloy of iron with boron, silicon, and phosphorus in the form of thin (e.g. 25 µm) foils. These materials have high magnetic susceptibility, very low co ercivity and high electrical resistance. The high resistance and thin foils lead to low losses by eddy currents when subjected to alternating magnetic fields.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Phase Oil Immersed Transformer</title>
      <link>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 16:29:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.distribution-transformer.com/post/three-phase-oil-immersed-transformer/</guid>
      <description>General oil immersed power transformer,based on know-how accumulated over decade years in oil immersed distribution transformer field, Farady’s oil-immersed transformers have been supplied to various industries including semiconductor, steel work, and petrochemical. Further, as an outstanding and comprehensive oil immersed distribution transformer solution provider, we respond to the oil immersed power transformer demanding requirements of our customers by developing and manufacturing both eco-friendly pole mounted distribution transformer and high-efficiency oil immersed power transformer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
